<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="Discover Serene Spaces Health Online journal for tips on living a balanced and healthy lifestyle. Explore articles on wellness, mindfulness, and self-care.Nutrition is essential for healthy living. Make informed food choices to nourish your body and mind for a balanced lifestyle.Stay active and healthy with regular exercise. Improve your physical and mental well-being by incorporating fitness into your daily routine.Achieve balance and peace of mind for a healthier, happier life. Explore tips and tricks for improved mental wellbeing in daily living.Stay healthy and disease-free by focusing on prevention through lifestyle choices, regular exercise, balanced diet, and routine medical check-ups.Hygiene is essential for healthy living - maintain cleanliness in your surroundings and personal habits to stay safe and well.Family: the heartbeat of home. Love, laughter, and support in every moment of living.Navigating relationships can be challenging but ultimately fulfilling. Learn to communicate, compromise, and grow together in the journey of life.Parenting is a journey of love, laughter, and challenges. Discover tips and resources to navigate the ups and downs of raising children in today's world.Explore the intricate and complex world of sibling dynamics in the context of living. Relationships, rivalries, and bonds all play a role.Exploring the importance of family traditions in shaping our lives and creating lasting memories.Learn how to effectively manage your household for a stress-free living experience. Tips and tricks to keep your home running smoothly.Living in harmony with our environment is essential for a sustainable future. Let's protect and preserve our planet for generations to come."Sustainability in living: making mindful choices to protect our planet and ensure a better future for generations to come. #sustainability #living"Navigating the impacts of climate change on our daily lives - from extreme weather to food production. Find ways to adapt and mitigate.Ecosystems - the intricate web of living organisms and their environment, showcasing the beauty and balance of nature's interconnectedness.Pollution affects our daily lives, from the air we breathe to the water we drink. It's time to take action and protect our environment.Conservation is key to preserving our planet and ensuring a sustainable future for all living beings."Discover the latest trends and tips for housing in our modern world. Find your perfect home and create a comfortable living space."Achieving the dream of home ownership brings stability, security, and a sense of belonging to your life.Renting: A flexible option for those seeking a place to live without the commitment of ownership. Find your perfect rental today!Elevate your living space with stunning interior design ideas and inspiration. Create a home that reflects your unique style and personality.Maintenance is essential for a well-functioning life. Stay on top of repairs and upkeep to ensure a comfortable living environment.Discover the best neighborhoods for living in your city! From bustling downtown areas to quiet suburbs, find your perfect community today.Stay up to date with the latest trends in fashion, lifestyle, and culture with our curated collection of trending news and stories.Achieving work-life balance is essential for a fulfilling life. Balancing career and personal time leads to better health, relationships, and overall happiness.Mastering time management is essential for living a balanced life. Learn how to prioritize tasks and make the most of your precious time.Learn effective stress management techniques for a healthier and happier life. Prioritize self-care and find balance in your daily living."Navigate your career path with purpose and passion. Unlock your potential for personal growth and professional success in living."Exploring hobbies and leisure activities to enhance your quality of life and well-being. Enjoying downtime and relaxation in daily living.Explore remote work opportunities for a flexible lifestyle. Work from anywhere and live your best life with remote job options.">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo6.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.d7566a0bc0db7fe3f83c57d0010a4a140 p,.d7566a0bc0db7fe3f83c57d0010a4a140 a,.d7566a0bc0db7fe3f83c57d0010a4a140 span,.d7566a0bc0db7fe3f83c57d0010a4a140 label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer{
background:#010101;
color:#ffffff;
}
.ce8a6da2c5938ccb5d916fdb1d6f16d3f a{
font-size:16px;
}
.d7566a0bc0db7fe3f83c57d0010a4a140 a,.ce8a6da2c5938ccb5d916fdb1d6f16d3f a{
color:#070707!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.nav-link{
color: #14646e!important;

}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
.yaccfba7d65fbf5509b3d3eb232e52564:hover{
box-shadow: 0 50.3px 50px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:8.4px;
padding-right:7.9px;
padding-top:5.2px;
padding-bottom:4.8px;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.5px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.1px 30.2px;
border-radius: 0;
}
.wa97f10d1d3df208afb9ade3af51bf9ec{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.ce8a6da2c5938ccb5d916fdb1d6f16d3f p,.ce8a6da2c5938ccb5d916fdb1d6f16d3f span,.ce8a6da2c5938ccb5d916fdb1d6f16d3f label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar-expand-lg navbar">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/index.html"  ><img alt="img/logo6.jpg" src="img/logo6.jpg"  width="150px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="align-items-center ml-auto d-flex navbar-nav"><li class="nav-item"><a class="vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408 nav-link" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/news.html"  >News</a></li>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Serene Spaces Health Online journal</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/index.html"  >Serene Spaces Health Online journal</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/nutrition.html"  >Nutrition</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/exercise.html"  >Exercise</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/mental-wellbeing.html"  >Mental wellbeing</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/disease-prevention.html"  >Disease prevention</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/hygiene.html"  >Hygiene</a>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="nav-link vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408 dropdown-toggle" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/family.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Family</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/family.html"  >Family</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/relationships.html"  >Relationships</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/parenting.html"  >Parenting</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/sibling-dynamics.html"  >Sibling dynamics</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/family-traditions.html"  >Family traditions</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/household-management.html"  >Household management</a>
  
<li class="nav-item dropdown ">
<a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/environment.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Environment</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/environment.html"  >Environment</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/sustainability.html"  >Sustainability</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/climate-change.html"  >Climate change</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/ecosystems.html"  >Ecosystems</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/pollution.html"  >Pollution</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/conservation.html"  >Conservation</a>
  
<li class=" nav-item dropdown">
<a class="dropdown-toggle vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408 nav-link" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/housing.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Housing</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/housing.html"  >Housing</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/home-ownership.html"  >Home ownership</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/renting.html"  >Renting</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/interior-design.html"  >Interior design</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/maintenance.html"  >Maintenance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/neighborhoods.html"  >Neighborhoods</a>
  
<li class="dropdown  nav-item">
<a class="nav-link vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408 dropdown-toggle" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/trending.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Trending</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/trending.html"  >Trending</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/work-life-balance.html"  >Work-life balance</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/time-management.html"  >Time management</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/stress-management.html"  >Stress management</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/career-development.html"  >Career development</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/leisure-activities.html"  >Leisure activities</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/remote-work-opportunities.html"  >Remote work opportunities</a>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="nav-link vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408" rel=nofollow href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li></ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Serene Spaces</h1>
<p>At Serene Spaces one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Serene Spaces and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: </p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Serene Spaces. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Serene Spaces, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Serene Spaces follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Serene Spaces.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Serene Spaces, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Serene Spaces has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Serene Spaces's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Serene Spaces does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Serene Spaces</br>
417-950-1684</br>
2937  Maple Street</br>
Cincinnati, OH, 45202</br>
United States</br>
</br>
<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="397358545c4a775e4c405c576a54584b4d7954585055175a5654">[email&#160;protected]</a></br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="container py-4 pt-5" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="vd3dfab1869bc4f8333d0753922591408" href="https://lifestyle.netlify.app/about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script data-cfasync="false" src="/cdn-cgi/scripts/5c5dd728/cloudflare-static/email-decode.min.js"></script><script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
